<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<tooltips>
	<param id="idInputLevel">
		Use to gain stage the guitar singal. A lightly strummed open chord should peak just above the "S" level for a single coil pickup, or "H" for humbucker pickup.
	</param>
	<param id="idOutputLevel">
		Use to gain stage the overall plugin master volume. This affects only how loud the plugin will sound.
	</param>
	<param id="idCabBrightness">
		Affects the microphone position in a way which relates to the overall brightness of the sound.
	</param>
	<param id="idCabDistance">
		Affects the microphone distance which will remove some lows and upper mids. This can have the effect of creating a clearer sound.
	</param>
	<param id="idCabDynamic">
		Affects how much the cabinet frequencies respond to the loudness of the signal. Increase to darken the distortion while leaving quiet parts unaffected.
	</param>
	<param id="idCabOnOff">
		Disables the cabinet emulation. Turn off if you want to run a separate cabinet emulation after the plugin.
	</param>
	<param id="idGainOverhead">
		Affects the amount of distortion in the later gain stages. Decrease for a high-gain sound.
	</param>
	<param id="idGainStages">
		The number of gain stages (tubes) the signal goes through. Each stage is voiced differently and can bring out more low end or tighter distortion.
	</param>
	<param id="idLowCut">
		How much of the lows are cut out from the pre amp stage. Increase to remove bass. Decrease to get fuller distortion.
	</param>
	<param id="idPreAmpDrive">
		The amount of distortion in the pre amp stage (a.k.a. amp gain). The plugin will adjust the output level to compensate.
	</param>
	<param id="idPreAmpGrit">
		Affects the amount of overhead available in the tubes. Decrease remove harsh artifacts from the tube distortion.
	</param>
	<param id="idPreAmpTight">
		Affects the time scale and depth of the tube amp dynamics. Increase to get a cleaner distoriton. Decrease for more touch sensitivity.
	</param>
	<param id="idPowerAmpDrive">
		The amount of distortion in the power amp stage (a.k.a. amp volume). The plugin will adjust the output level to compensate.
	</param>
	<param id="idPowerAmpTight">
		Affects the time scale and depth of the power amp dynamics. Has large effect on the sag compression attack and release.
	</param>
	<param id="idPowerAmpSag">
		Affects how much the amplified level drop in response to a large signal. Increase for a more compressed sound. Not as effectie with low power amp drive or large pre amp drive.
	</param>
	<param id="idTsHigh">
		The amount of high end going into the power amp. Increase for a brighter tone. Decrase to reduce harsh distortion noise.
	</param>
	<param id="idTsMid">
		The amount of mids going into the power amp. Increase for a more aggressive, punchier tone. Can increase sustain when the power amp drive is high.
	</param>
	<param id="idTsLow">
		The amount of bass going into the power amp. Increase for a fuller sound. Decrease for more definition and more brightness.
	</param>
	<param id="idTsPresence">
		The amoumt of signal in the higher mids, lower highs. Increase for more definition, more detail. Decrease to reduce brittle harshness.
	</param>
	<param id="idTsSelection">
        Tone stack: 0 for a Fender-like mids scoop, 5 for a Marshall-like tone with mids, 10 for an AC30-like tone with added mids control.
	</param>
</tooltips>
